Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 67, folder: 38 (Box 67, Folder 38)
  - Item 14: 1,663,016 Shares of USI Common Stock Tendered, Publication (Box 67, Folder 38)
    Jauary 15, 1979. Item is in English.
- Box: 67, folder: 39 (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: U.S. Industries Selects Chief at Special Meeting, Publication (Box 67, Folder 39)
    April 29, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Ahead of Schedule., Publication (Box 67, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: The Total Challenge of Automation, Publication (Box 67, Folder 39)
    By John I. Snyder, Jr. November 19, 1963. Item is in English.
- Box: 67, folder: 40 (Box 67, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: U.S. Industries, Machinists' Union Cooperate in Automation Study: Survey to Help Readjust Displaced Workers, Publication (Box 67, Folder 40)
    By Ralph Katz. Item is in English.
- Box: 67, folder: 41 (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: U.S. Industries, Inc. Annual Report 1969, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Item 2: USI Announces Record First Quarter Results, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
    April 17, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: USI, Inc. Successful People United for Greater Growth, Annual Report 1968, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Item 4: U.S. Industries, Inc., to Purchase 80% of Health Spa Company, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Item 5: USI Enters Recreational Boating Market, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
    June 2, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Delwood Furniture Company, Inc. Files Initial Public Offering, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
    November 1, 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: U.S. Industries Showed Record Sales and Earnings in 1971, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
    February 23, 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: U.S. Industries had record Sales and Earnings in 1971--Eighth Consecutive Record Year Predicted in 1972, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
    January 26, 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: U.S. Industries Achieves Record Sales and Earnings in Third Quarter and First Nine Months of 1971, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
    October 20, 1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: U.S. Industries Sers Sales and Profit Records in Third Quarter as Earnings per Share Rise 10% to 65 Cents, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
    October 18, 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Preliminary Results of U.S. Industries, Inc., Indicate Declines in Net Income and Earnings per Share from 1972--No Proxy Contest Expected, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
    January 10, 1974. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: USI Completes Sale of Three Trucking Companies, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
    May 3, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Mid-Year Review, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
  - Item 14: A Big Step, Publication (Box 67, Folder 41)
- Box: 67, folder: 42 (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Successful People United for a Greater Growth: Annual Report 1967, Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Item 2: Annual Report 1964, Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Item 3: Report to Shareholders, Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
    November 20, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Report to the Shareholders, Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
    May 22, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Annual Report 1963, Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Item 6: U.S. Industries, Inc., Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
    June 29, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Report to the Share Holders, Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
    August 21, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Annual Report 1962, Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Item 9: Annual Report 1966, Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
  - Item 10: Annual Report 1972, Publication (Box 67, Folder 42)
- Box: 67, folder: 43 (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Career Opportunities in the United States Information Agency, Publication (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Item 2: Foreign Service Career Opportunities in the United States Information Agency, Publication (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Item 3: Hearing on Bills to Promote the Foreign Policy of the United States by Strengthening and Improving the Foreign Service Personnel System of the U.S. Information Agency Through Establishment of a Foreign Service Information Officer Corps, Publication (Box 67, Folder 43)
    September 28, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: USIA Foreign Service Personnel System Report No. 715, Publication (Box 67, Folder 43)
  - Item 5: Career Intern Program in Broadcasting, Publication (Box 67, Folder 43)
- Box: 67, folder: 44 (Box 67, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: United States Section of the Inter-American Council of Commerce and Production, Publication (Box 67, Folder 44)
- Box: 67, folder: 45 (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Inter-American Bulletin, Publication (Box 67, Folder 45)
    October-November 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Inter-American Bulletin, Publication (Box 67, Folder 45)
    August-September 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Inter-American Bulletin, Publication (Box 67, Folder 45)
    April 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Inter-American Bulletin, Publication (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - Item 5: Proceedings of the VIII Plenary Meeting, Publication (Box 67, Folder 45)
    July 15-19, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Inter-American Bulletin, Publication (Box 67, Folder 45)
    June-July 1964. Item is in English.
- Box: 67, folder: 46 (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Programmers: Internal Revenue Service. U.S. Treasury Department, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 2: The Estate Tax Examiner: Opportunity for Men and Women Law School Graduates, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 3: The Revenue Officer, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 4: The Revenue Agent: A Career in Professional Accounting, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 5: The Tax Technician, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 6: A Career and A Sense of Purpose, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 7: Revenue Officer, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 8: Revenue Agent, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 9: Revenue Agent, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 10: Attorney Estate Tax, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
  - Item 11: A New Dimension in Taxation, Publication (Box 67, Folder 46)
- Box: 67, folder: 47 (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Description of the Central and Field Organization of the Interstaate Commerce Commission, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
    August 2, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Description of the Central and Field Organization of the Interstaate Commerce Commission, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - Item 3: Description of the Central and Field Organization of the Interstate Commerce Commission, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
    Revised July 31, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Interstate Commerce Commission, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - Item 5: What isI.C.C.: Questions and Answers about the Interstate Commerce Commission, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - Item 6: Exercised in Observance of the 75th Anniversary of the Interstate Commerce Commission, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - Item 7: Interstate Commerce Commission: 75 Years of Regulatory Service in the Public Interest, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - Item 8: Membership - Interstate Commerce Commission, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - Item 9: The Role of the ICC Hearing Examiner, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
    October 25, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: An American Story: The Story of the Independent Telephone Industry in the United States, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
  - Item 11: Description of the Central and Field Organization of the Interstaate Commerce Commission, Publication (Box 67, Folder 47)
    January 1, 1964. Item is in English.